[
    {
      "ID": "1",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 20mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "6m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "2",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 20mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "6m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "3",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 20mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "12m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "4",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 30mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "9m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "5",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 30mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "14m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "6",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 30mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "23m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "7",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 40mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "12m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "8",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 40mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "24m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "9",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 40mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "36m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "10",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 50mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "15m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "11",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 50mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "38m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "12",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 50mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "53m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "13",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 60mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "18m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "14",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 60mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "55m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "15",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 60mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "73m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "16",
      "Question": "Thinking Distance of 70mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "21m"
    },  
    {
      "ID": "17",
      "Question": "Braking Distance of 70mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "75m"
    },
    {
      "ID": "18",
      "Question": "Overall Stopping Distance of 70mph (Dry)?",
      "Answer": "96m"
    }
]